So now we are going to see the same valid example one more time, and this time we are going to see
how secure the code is and if we can break the security or not.
So this is the valid card, as you can see, and it's also printing the valid Uid, right.
And this is another card.
Let's just place it.
And you can see it's an invalid card and it's also printing the Uid of invalid card.
So we are going to use magic card this time.
And magic cards are the special type of RFID cards in which we can update the Uid of any card.
Right.
So as I told you before, that mifare cards in Mifare cards, we cannot update the Uid, but in magic
cards we can update the Uid.
Right.
So that's why we are going to use magic cards and we will update the of our valid card into this card.
Using the device which you can see it over here.
Right.
So we will use this device to update the magic card.
Let's just use this device and let's just turn on this device.
Right.
So as you can see, it's an invalid card and let's just press okay, on the device.
And what you have to do is simple.
You have to just read.
And it's a valid card, as you can see.
And what we will do is first we will read the Uid in this device of a valid card.
Let's just do it one more time.
And over here you can see, write, read success, and you can see the Uid of the valid card.
And what we will do is we will write the Uid in this invalid card.
So we will place the card below the device and we will press the right button and you can see the right
success message.
Right.
And now let's just check this card one more time.
And as you can see, the cards get valid and we can see the changed Uid and we can easily break the
security using the magic cards.
So in the next video we are going to see how we can utilize the full potential of RFID cards and we
will use blocks and sectors to store our data and we will use keys to secure our data.
Right.
So in the next video, we are going to see how we can make our RFID card more secure.